(Raj:)-How could you not put in an abort?
-I made a boo-boo, all right?
I think the board will really appreciate
how well we're using that NSA grant.
(Leonard:)Right here
we have a micro-controlled plasma--
(Bernadette:)Wow.
Looks like the Ganges on laundry day.
(Leonard:)At least they don't know it was you.
SHELDON [OVER COMPUTER]:
Hello, Kripke.
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)This classic prank comes to you...
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)...from the malevolent mind
of Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)If you'd like to see the look
on your stupid face...
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)...this video is being instantly uploaded
to YouTube.
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)Oh, and a hat tip to Leonard Hofstadter
and Raj Koothrappali...
(Sheldon(on Kripke's computer in the lab):)...for their support and encouragement
in this enterprise.
(Raj:)Well, I'm going back to India.
What's your plan?